Pete Welding collection, 1958-1995
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 8: Sound recordings
  - Subseries 1: Artists, bands, and interviews
    - Tom's Records / Stony Island Boys / #1, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR277; RXH 4163; 1 sound tape reel (01:37:08): analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono; 7 in.
      00:12:00 "The Old K-C" - Jess Young's Tennessee Band ("I thought I heard that old K-C blow, yes Lord...and she blowed like she never blowed no more") (Columbia 15431-D)
      00:15:07 "Lovin' Henry" - Jess Young's Tennessee Band ("Has anybody seen my lovin' Henry, has anybody seen my lovin' man") Columbia 15431-D)
      00:17:58 "I Cannot Call Her Mother" - Charlie Poole And The North Carolina Ramblers ("The marriage ride is over") (Columbia 15307-D)
      00:21:00 "What Is Home Without Babies" - Charlie Poole And The North Carolina Ramblers ("All alone in a mansion, no one to love and caress") (Columbia 15307-D)
      00:24:27 "The New Market Wreck" - George Reneau ("The Southern Railway had a wreck, at 10 o'clock one morn") (Vocalion 14930)
      00:27:38 "The Bald-Headed End of the Broom" - George Reneau ("Now it is a very funny thing, catching the young and old") (Vocalion 14930)
      00:30:48 "Bury Me in the Hillbilly Way" - Billy Cox and Cliff Hobbs ("One evening a young man lay dying, beneath the root there lay in the rain") (Vocalion 05055)
      00:33:32 "Old Pinto and Me" - Billy Cox and Cliff Hobbs ("Oh pinto someday there'll be a great change, but I love my old home way out on the range") (Vocalion 05055)
      00:36:18 "Frankie Silvers" - Byrd Moore and His Hot Shots ("...My sun goes down, my days are past...I am gonna see this world at last...why did you take my life away") (Columbia 15536-D)
      00:39:34 "The Hills of Tennessee" - Byrd Moore and His Hot Shots ("On one bright and merry May") (Columbia 15536-D)
      00:42:23 "Want My Black Baby Back" - Walter Couch and Wilks Ramblers ("Hambone's sidetracked, ain't that a shame, why don't you get your lady of your own") (Bluebird B7095)
      00:44:36 "Lonesome Trail" - Walter Couch and Wilks Ramblers ("...There's just one thing I wanna hear you say before I say goodbye, now come to me my little girl, and say you love me true") (Bluebird B7095)
      00:47:08 "I'll Be All Smiles Tonight" - The Reed Children ("I'll deck my brow with roses...though my heart will break tomorrow, I will be all smiles tonight") (Columbia 15525-D)
      00:50:08 "I Once Did Have a Sweetheart" - The Reed Children ("I once have a sweetheart, a sweetheart brave and true...he was like most other boys...when he came to say good bye, my heart did overflow") (Columbia 15525-D)
      00:53:06 "It's Hard to Love and Can't Be Loved" - Buster Carter and Preston Young ("Don't you see that lonesome dove, ...he's mourning for his own true, just like I mourn for mine") [cuts off abruptly] (Columbia 15690-D)
      00:56:10 "I'll Roll in My Sweet Baby's Arms" - Buster Carter and Preston Young ("Ain't gonna work on the railroad, ain't work on it long, lay around my shack till that mail train comes back and I'll roll in my sweet baby's arms") (Columbia 15690-D)
      00:59:15 "A Lazy Farmer Boy" - Buster Carter and Preston Young ("Now I'll sing a little song, but it ain't there long about a lazy farmer...that young man was always well") (Columbia 15702-D)
      01:02:16 "It Won't Hurt No More" - Buster Carter and Preston Young ("Hello doc, I've got a bad tooth, I want you to look and see what to do") (Columbia 15702-D)
      01:05:23 "Buckin' Mule" - Gid Tanner (Columbia 15237-D)
      01:08:35 "Casey Jones" - Gid Tanner ("Train going south, Birmingham, the first stop, come all you rounders if you want to hear, story told about a brave engineer") (Columbia 15237-D)
      01:11:20 "Just Make My People Think You Care" - Dewey and Gassie Bassett ("Oh, won't you come my little darling, won't you come and bathe my brow, before they tell me I am dying, won't you come and say goodbye") (Bluebird B8235)
      01:13:42 "Sympathy" - Dewey and Gassie Bassett ("You are all I have but now I feel so bad, all that I'm asking is sympathy") (Bluebird B8235)
      01:16:17 "The Man Who Wrote Home Sweet Home Never Was A Married Man" - Charlie Parker and Mack Woolbright ("Man gets up early in the morning and leaves his wife in bed...he never had no loving wife to beat him with a frying pan, she'll meet you at the door when you [...] come in") (Columbia 15236-D)
      01:19:28 "Ticklish Reuben" - Charlie Parker and Mack Woolbright("My name is Ticklish Reuben from way down in old Vermont") (Columbia 15236-D)
      01:22:07 "Single Life" - Roba Stanley ("...single life is lovely, I am single and no man's wife") (Okeh 40436)
      01:25:14 "Little Frankie" - Roba Stanley and Bill Patterson ("Frankie woke up one morning...he's my man but he done me wrong") [poor sound quality] (Okeh 40436)
      01:28:28 "Wish to the Lord I Had Never Been Born" - Luther B. Clarke, accompanied by the Blue Ridge Highballers (Columbia 15096-D)
      01:31:24 "Going Down To Lynchburg Town"/Intro: "Don't Let Your Deal Go Down" - Luther B. Clarke, accompanied by the Blue Ridge Highballers (Columbia 15096-D)
      01:34:18 "Nellie Dare" - Elizie Floyd and Leo Boswell ("Miss Nellie since leaving the city, I've found I've changed my mind, I hope you won't think me too fickle, or think me the least unkind") (Columbia 15150)
      01:37:08 End
    - Tom's Records #2, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR656; RXH 5533; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
    - Tom's Records #3 / Roy Burrows Quintet - Country Music Dubs #3, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR599; RXH 5460; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
    - Six unidentified jazz songs, circa 1970s, AFC 2011/053: SR786; RAA 59324; 1 sound tape reel (00:35:20): analog, 15 ips, half track, stereo; 10 in.
      Vendor's digitization note: The program is distorted at times, and there is hiss from the source tape. There is also a test tone on the tape.
    - Various test tones, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR580; RXH 5441; 1 sound tape reel (00:03:55): analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      Collector's original ID number: 68.
      Archivist's note: Various test frequencies, measured in kHz, with an announcement preceding each tone.
    - Henry Townsend interview #1, July 27, 1967, AFC 2011/053: SR045; RXH 3184; on one side of 1 sound tape reel (00:32:43): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
      Logger's note: This is the first part of a two-part interview Pete Welding (PW) did with Henry Townsend (HT), conducted in St. Louis, Missouri. Most of the interview is about Robert Johnson (RJ). A third person, called Joe, was present, [not Big Joe Williams]. (Note: It is difficult to hear and understand Joe, as he does not have a microphone.)
      Start PW asks about HT meeting RJ. HT says they met at a house party, where they were both to perform, in the early to mid-1930s. They talk at length about RJ. HT also mentions Roosevelt Sykes and Booker T. Washington.
      00:04:30 PW asks about the music RJ was playing that night. HT's response includes that RJ was playing slide guitar.
      00:06:12 PW asks how the people responded to the slide guitar. HT says, "they were wild about him." HT talks about playing with RJ.
      00:09:42 PW asks about the numbers (songs) that RJ performed. HT responds and talks about playing with RJ.
      00:11:52 PW asks if RJ was fairly well paid. HT responds and then talks about where RJ was living.
      00:14:30 PW asks what kind of impression RJ's music made on HT. HT replies that he was interested both RJ's guitar and his singing. They talk about what made RJ's Mississippi Blues different from other musicians. HT responds at length.
      00:19:05 PW asks about HT picking up RJ's music. HT responds that he was mostly trying to learn execution. He says that RJ was an easy going guy.
      00:21:10 HT talks about other people RJ hung out with. He talks about playing in the Harlem Club in Illinois.
      00:23:10 They talk about Robert Lockwood Jr. and Roosevelt Sykes. They talk about how to contact Robert Lockwood and RJ.
      00:29:13 They talk about RJ's travelling and old Mississippi musicians RJ may have known. HT says that RJ supported himself just playing music on his guitar.
      00:32:43 End
    - Henry Townsend interview #2, July 27, 1967, AFC 2011/053: SR046; RXH 3185; on one side of 1 sound tape reel (00:25:10): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
      Logger's note: This is the second part of a two-part interview Pete Welding (PW) did with Henry Townsend (HT), conducted in St. Louis, Missouri.
      Start PW, HT and Joe are talking about RL. They mention Honeyboy Edwards. They talk about Johnson as a "ladies man." They talk about RJ's age at the time he died.
      00:02:43 PW asks about RJ's working on songs "when he was here." HT responds. He says the RJ was able to work on inspiration and could put a song together "just like that." He explains.
      00:05:53 HT says that his acquaintance with RJ was brief. RJ was a "pretty nice guy." PW asks why HT thought RJ was young when he died. HT thought RJ was young when they met. HT explains and talks about RJ's character.
      00:08:20 PW asks if HT got the impression that RJ took a lot of pride in his music. HT replies at length.
      00:09:50 PW asks HT if he and RJ rehearsed together. HT responds.
      00:11:00 PW asks if there were any other musicians around town (i.e., St. Louis) that RJ worked with in that period. HT responds. They talk about Jimmy Yancey, a piano player. They also talk about Alonzo Yancey.
      00:12:42 PW asks HT if there is anything else HT can tell him about RJ. HT responds.
      00:13:34 PW asks about Hi Henry Brown. Joe responds. They also talk about Ike Rodgers. PW asks about Henry Spalding. HT responds, as does Joe. They mention Nick Bones, Clifford Gibson and Roosevelt Sykes. They discuss Clifford Gibson at length and talk about his dog.
      00:21:55 PW asks what other musicians were around in the 1920s and 1930s. He mentions Pinetop Sparks. PW asks about Pinetop Sparks and his sister.
      00:25:10 End
    - Traditional Negro Sacred Songs (1), undated, AFC 2011/053: SR478; RXH 4718; 1 sound tape reel (00:30:10): analog, 7 1/2 ips, mono; 7 in.
      Start "Nobody's Fault But My Own" by Clay and Scott
      00:02:47 "Motherless Children" by Connie Williams (guitar)
      00:04:55 "Motherless Children" by Clay and Scott
      00:07:39 "Keep Your Lamp Trimmed and Burning" by Connie Williams (accor)
      00:09:40 "Sometimes My Burden's So Hard to Bear" by Mrs. F. Coleman
      00:12:08 "Pack up, Church, And Let's Go Home" by Connie Williams (guitar)
      00:13:48 "Just a Talk With Jesus" by Clay and Scott
      00:16:35 "Some Of These Days" by Mrs. Ella Coleman
      00:19:13 "Farther Along" by Connie Williams
      00:22:12 "I'm So Glad Trouble Don't Last Always" by Clay and Scott
      00:25:22 "Roll Jordon Roll" by Mrs. Coleman
      00:27:33 "Roll Jordon Roll" by an unidentified male singing group
    - Traditional Negro Sacred Songs (2), undated, AFC 2011/053: SR479; RXH 4719; 1 sound tape reel (00:08:25): analog, 7 1/2 ips, mono; 7 in.
      Start "Just A Closer Walk With Thee" by C. Wilsons [?]
      00:02:15 "Angels Are Looking At Me" by Ella Coleman
      00:04:15 "The Lord Will Make A Way" by Clay and Scott [accompanied by accordion]
      00:08:25 End
    - Traveling Through The Jungle: Negro Fife And Drum Band Music From The Deep South, released by Testament Records(T-2223-A), 1974, AFC 2011/053: SR492; RXH 4732; 1 sound tape reel (00:21:16): analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      Dub copy of final edited and sequenced Side 1; see the note for SR491. Collector's original number: 229
      00:00:27 "Old Hen Cackled, Laid A Double Egg"
      00:02:22 unidentified tune
      00:04:40 "Shout, Lula With The Red Dress On"
      00:06:33 "Buck Dance"
      00:08:04 "I Love Jesus, Yes, I Do"
      00:10:22 "Wake Up, Sal, Day Done Come, Let Me Chew Your Rosin Some"
      00:11:33 "Old Lady Dinah Sitting By The Fire"
      00:12:38 "Jesse James"
      00:14:24 "Come On Boys, Let's Go To The Ball"
      00:15:56 "The Death March"
      00:17:42 "Emmaline, Take Your Time"
      00:19:22 "The Sidewalks Of New York"
    - Traveling Through The Jungle: Negro Fife And Drum Band Music From The Deep South, released by Testament Records(T-2223-B), 1974, AFC 2011/053: SR491; RXH 4731; 1 sound tape reel (00:22:09): analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      Dub copy of final edited and sequenced Side 2. See the notes for SR492.
      Start "My Babe" - vocals and fife performed by Napoleon Strickland]
      00:04:40 "Traveling Through The Jungle" [The fife is possibly performed by Napoleon Strickland. Percussion: waste basket performed by Fred McDowell.]
      00:06:38 "Sitting On Top Of The World" - vocals, whistling, percussion (washtub) performed by Compton Jones
      00:09:10 "Late At Midnight, Just A Little 'Fore Day"
      00:13:15 "Granny, Will Your Dog Bite"
      00:16:02 "Number Five" - whistling, percussion (washtub) performed by Compton Jones
      00:18:25 "When The Saints Go Marching In"
      00:22:09 End
    - Traveling Through the Jungle: Negro Fife and Drum Band Music from the Deep South: dub of material on Testament T-2223 A and B, 1974, AFC 2011/053: SR514; RXH 5376; 1 sound tape reel: analog (00:45:34): 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      Archivist's note: These recordings were collected between 1942 and 1970, and released on the Testament label. Side 2 of this tape has not yet been digitized.
      Note from the tape box: "material is not in order used on LP; sequence indicated on log sheet included." Collector's original ID number: 136.
      Vendor's digitization note: There is no right channel on the tape from the start of the program to 00:09:17. The program is distorted at times, with static, clicks, and pops on the tape.
      Start "Come On Boys, Let's Go To The Ball" - Alec Askew and Willie Head (AFS 06672 A1)
      00:01:37 "Emmaline, Take Your Time" - Sid Hemphill (AFS 06672 A4)
      00:03:26 "Jesse James" - Sid Hemphill's Band (AFS 06673 A1)
      00:05:19 "The Sidewalks Of New York" - Sid Hemphill's Band; personnel: Sid Hemphill, Lucius Smith, Will Reed, Alec Askew (AFS 06673 A3)
      00:07:29 "The Death March" - Sid Hemphill's Band
      00:09:19 "Wake Up Sal, Day Done Come, Let Me Chew Your Rosin Some" - J.W. Jones (70-10)
      00:10:36 "I Love Jesus, Yes I Do" - Ephram Carter, J.W. Jonas, James Jones, Floyd Bussey (70-12)
      00:12:53 "Old Hen Cackled, Laid A Double Egg" - Ephram Carter, J.W. Jonas, James Jones, Floyd Bussey (70-12)
      00:14:47 "Old Lady Dinah Sitting By The Fire" - Ephram Carter, J.W. Jonas, James Jones, Floyd Bussey (70-12)
      00:16:57 "Buck Dance" - J.W. Jones, dancing; Ephram Carter, body slaps and speech (70-12)
      00:18:38 "Short, Lula With The Red Dress On" - Ephram Carter (70-13)
      00:20:41 unknown piece - Napoleon Strickland, Othar Turner, and R.L. Boyce (70-13)
      00:22:55 "Sitting On Top Of The World" - Compton Jones and Othar Turner (70-48)
      00:29:49 "Number 5" - Compton Jones (70-47)
      00:27:44 "Traveling Through The Jungle" - Napoleon Strickland and Fred McDowell (69-18)
      00:29:49 "Late At Midnight, Just A Little 'Fore Day" - Othar Turner, Arthur Williams, and Arthur Boyce (70-4)
      00:34:31 "Granny, Will Your Dog Bite" - Napoleon Strickland, Othar Turner, and R.L. Boyce(70-45)
      00:37:17 "My Babe" - Napoleon Strickland, Othar Turner, and R.L. Boyce(70-45)
      00:41:53 "When The Saints Go Marching In" - Napoleon Strickland, Jimmie Buford, and R.L. Boyce(70-45)
      00:45:34 End
    - Lennie Tristano - Lester Young - "Hotel Chatterbox" airshot, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR705; RXH 5582; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      This tape seems to be a compilation of dub recordings.
    - Lennie Tristano -- Capitol Records, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR342; RXH 4227; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:24:44, Side 2: 00:19:58): analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 5 in.
      Unissued recordings by Lennie Tristano (piano, bass, and drums; guitar on tracks 1-3, 5, 7, 9), 16 songs. Capitol Records.
      Vendor's digitization note: The program is distorted at times, with significant hiss from the tape.
      Start "Stairway To The Stars"
      00:03:09 "Somebody Love Me"
      00:06:10 "Laura"
      00:08:52 Romantic classical theme adaption on pop song
      00:11:46 "Don't Blame Me"
      00:14:45 "Little Girl"
      00:16:35 "Polka Dots and Moonbeams"
      00:19:38 "Down by the Old Mill Stream"
      00:21:55 "If I Should Lose You" (runs off)
      00:24:44 End
      Start instrumental song
      00:03:11 instrumental song
      00:05:29 instrumental song
      00:08:38 instrumental song
      00:11:24 instrumental song
      00:14:18 instrumental song
      00:17:01 instrumental song
      00:19:58 End
    - Tri-Tone Social Club (Tom Shepherd/Bruce Cale/Bill Moser), undated, AFC 2011/053: SR217; RXH 4100; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:24:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      "Tri-Tone Social Club" is named on the tape box; it is unclear if this is the name of a project or an album. According to documentation Cale plays bass viol, Bill Moser plays drums, and Tom Shepherd plays reeds. This seems to be an unreleased recording.
      Start "Valma" [?] (Shepherd)
      00:04:15 Bells begins to play (Cale)
      00:09:06 "Windows"
      00:15:32 "Windows"
      00:20:10 Unidentified song (Shepherd)
      00:23:43 End
    - "In Concert": Ike and Tina Turner; The Staple Singers, December 14, 1973, AFC 2011/053: SR151; RXH 4034; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:30:44): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Archivist's note: The ABC-TV show "In Concert" featured concert performances that were recorded live and subsequently broadcast. December 14, 1973 was probably the broadcast date. While "In Concert" was created by Don Kirshner it is not the same show as "Don Kirshner's Rock Concert." See SR152 and SR153.
      Start "River Deep, Mountain High," by Ike and Tina Turner. The recording begins with the song in progress.
      00:03:27 "Get Back," by Ike and Tina Turner
      00:06:40 "Try to Get to Know Each Other," by Ike and Tina Turner
      00:09:16 "Proud Mary," by Ike and Tina Turner
      00:15:36 "Ooh La De Da," by The Staple Singers
      00:17:50 "Respect Yourself," by The Staple Singers
      00:21:35 "I'll Take You There," by The Staple Singers
      00:30:44 End
    - Johnny Turner interview, circa mid-1970s, AFC 2011/053: SR049; RXH 3188; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:54:54; Side 2: 00:06:00): analog, 3 3/4 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
      Start Piano music.
      00:00:22 PW ask JT bout his background. JT responds. He was born in Altheimer, Arkansas. His father was a sharecropper. At age 12 his family moved to Little Rock. He started listening to music when he was young. JT tells who he heard. He was interested in playing the harmonica; this was around 1954 or 1955.
      00:04:40 They talk about modern blues that JT heard on the radio. He listened to King Biscuit. JT talks about learning to play the harmonica. He started playing when he was about 9 years old. Later he stared playing the guitar.
      00:06:20 JT says he made a guitar out of a board and wire. It was called a "post guitar." They talk about musicians who played this kind of guitar.
      00:08:04 PW asks JT when he got a hold of a real guitar. JT responds that it was after he moved to Little Rock. He started playing a real guitar using a neighbor's guitar. He played a lot of Jim Reed's music.
      00:09:35 JT met Fen (Fenton) Robinson who showed him a lot. He had already started recording. They talk about Fen Robinson. JT played bass guitar with Robinson. It was a solid-body instrument with unusual strings and tuning.
      00:14:26 PW ask JT how long he played with Fen. JT says that it was for a couple of years. His skill as musician improved during this time. He also played with other musicians. JT talks about a female singer called Sweet Lorraine.
      00:17:22 PW asks what music JT was listening to. JT responds that he listened mostly to the radio. He listened to blues, and rock and roll, like Little Richard. JT says that he played both blues and rock and roll. They talk about what JT listened to on the radio. They talk about black radio stations and white radio stations.
      00:21:52 They talk about black jazz on the radio. However, JT listened mostly to blues and rock and roll. JT says the only records he would buy were B.B. King and Jimmy Reed. JT learned to play B.B. King songs note-for-note, but could not get King's feel.
      00:25:06 JT talks about getting jobs (gigs) on his own. Only the best musicians played during the week. Everyone got work on the weekends. JT talks about playing with musicians who came through town (Little Rock).
      00:28:29 PW asks JT when started playing with Fenton Robinson. JT says he was 15 or 16 years old and played with him for several years. In 1965 JT moved to California. He talks about a band The Blue Notes.
      00:30:32 JT got work in a club in San Pedro, California. He then worked with Joe Houston and went back onto the road. There was not a market for blues in California, so they played mostly soul music.
      00:33:45 They talk about JT's trips back to Little Rock. There was less interest in the blues than "back then." They talk about making recording in Little Rock.
      00:35:18 JT says he made several records in little Rock before he moved to California. He does not know if they were issued. He made them for A & M Records.
      00:36:48 PW asks JT to describe the music scene in California. JT says "this is difficult." People in California go to clubs, very much on the weekends. A lot of former blues singers are now singing soul. Tyrone Davis is big.
      00:40:28 They talk about a place called Home of the Blues. JT says that her recorded there. They talk about Larry Davidson. Hey talk about a blues band, Blues With a Feeling. JT talks about Big John [who joins in this interview].
      00:43:25 They talk about blues styles that JT plays. They talk about JT developing his own style.
      00:46:25 JT talks about what he did to develop his own blues style. JT started studying music. He wanted to get away from the B.B. King style. He learned a lot playing with a saxophone.
      00:50:10 JT says that the last time he went back to Arkansas he found that the same songs sounded differently in Little Rock than they did in Louisiana. They talk about horns being added to a band
      00:54:54 End
      Start PW and JT talk about a band called Blues with a Feeling. JT moved to Pasadena. The band has been together for about two years. They talk about the band and some of the places they played. They talk about people's nicknames.
      00:06:00 End
    - Johnny Turner interview, circa 1970s, AFC 2011/053: SR732; RXH 5609; 1 sound tape reel (acetate; Side 1: 00:28:57, Side 2: 00:27:54): analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in.
    - Johnny Turner - Zaven Jambazian (#1) Mississippi Sheiks (#22-A), March 10, 1974, AFC 2011/053: SR790; RAA 59328; 1 sound tape reel (00:37:16): analog, 15 ips, half-track, stereo; 10 in.
      Pete Welding played guitar on this recording.
    - Apresentando - Rosinha de Valença (Elenco ME-16, 1963 ) / 3rd Festival da Musica Popular Brasileira (Phillips R 765.014L, 1967 ), 1963, 1967, AFC 2011/053: SR567; RXH 5428; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
    - Jimmy Walker, #7, April 1, 1962, AFC 2011/053: SR278; RXH 4164; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:29:22): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.
      Logger's note: Boogie woogie tunes performed by Jimmy Walker, and fragments of interviews.
      Start An unidentified instrumental boogie woogie piece performed on the piano.
      00:02:54 "I'm Leaving You, Baby" performed by Jimmy Walker